Guide to the Cornell University Department of Natural Resources records, 1909-1995.
Cornell University Department of Natural Resources records, 1909-1995.
- Barrows Farm Measurements, 61 (Box 17)
- Comstock Knoll Plantation and Christmas Trees, 1923, 62 (Box 17)
- Fense Posts - General, 63 (Box 17)
- Wood Preservatives and Treating - General, 64 (Box 17)
- Oil-bourne Preservatives, 65 (Box 17)
- Wood Preservatives - Osmuse, 66 (Box 17)
- Cedar Post Controversy, 67 (Box 17)
- Northeastern Coordinated Wood Preservation Investigations, 68 (Box 17)
- Highway Guard Posts, 69 (Box 17)
- Peeling, Sharpening Fence Posts and Hole Digging, 70 (Box 17)
- Raymond Correspondence, 1933, 71 (Box 17)
- Research and Silviculturist Statements - Varna Plots, 72 (Box 17)
- Black Locust Plantations, 73 (Box 17)
- Statistical Methods, 74 (Box 17)
- Shipmast Locust Plantation - Cleon Shuster - Seneca Falls, 75 (Box 17)
- Gravity or End-flow Treatment of Fence Posts, 76 (Box 17)
- Pennsylvania State Farm Show 1955, 77 (Box 17)
- Pull Up or Capillary Treatment of Fence Posts, 78 (Box 17)
- Hardwood Demonstration, 1936, 79 (Box 17)
- Double Diffusion Treatment of Fence Posts, 80 (Box 17)
- Cold Soaking Treatment of Fence Posts, 81 (Box 17)
- Pressure Treatment of Fence Posts, 82 (Box 17)
- Hot and Cold Bath Treatment, 83 (Box 17)
- Osmose Process - Fence Post Treatment, 84 (Box 17)
- Oregon Salt Method - Fence Post Treatment, 85 (Box 17)
- Fence Post Treating Demonstrations, 86 (Box 17)
- Fence Post Survey, 87 (Box 17)
- Chatauqua County Grape Steak Treating, 88 (Box 17)
- Fence Post Preservatives - Miscellaneous, 89 (Box 17)
- Pentachlorphenol Compounds - Treating Wood in Greenhouses, 90 (Box 17)
- Treated Posts - Service Tests, 91 (Box 17)
- Reply from Wood Preservatives Co's, 92 (Box 17)
- Wood Preservatives - Prices, 93 (Box 17)
- Soil Conservation - Photographs, 94 (Box 17)
- Trapping - Drawings, 95 (Box 17)
- Future Forests - Tree Planting Photographs, 96 (Box 17)
- Conservation Workshops - Photographs, 97 (Box 17)
- Extension Bulletin - Woodlots, 98 (Box 17)
- 4-H Bulletin - Woodlot Management, 99 (Box 17)
- 4-H Bulltein - Tree Indentification, Drawings, 100 (Box 17)
- Tree Planting Photographs, 101 (Box 17)
- Wood Lots - Orleans County through Yates County, 102 (Box 17)
- Conservation Workshop, 1953, 103 (Box 17)
- Agricultural Hour - Radio Talks, 104 (Box 17)
- Conservation Workshop, 1953, 105 (Box 18)
- Cooperative Extension Activities in New York State, 106 (Box 18)
- Annual Report - Department of Conservation, 1950-1951, 107 (Box 18)
- Forestry Field Days, 108 (Box 18)
- Farm Bureau Articles, 109 (Box 18)
- Extension Foresters - Circular Letters, 110 (Box 18)
- Radio Talks, 1953-1958, 111 (Box 18)
- Circular Letter File, 1959-1961; Harlan B. Brumsted, 112 (Box 18)
- Outdoors Today, 113 (Box 18)
- Forest Practice Act, 114 (Box 18)
- Outdoors Today, 115 (Box 18)
- Monthly Reports - Brumsted, Cunningham, Winch, 1956-1957, 116 (Box 18)
- Monthly Reports - Winch, Brumsted, Cunningham, Hamilton, Kellogg, Ayers, Morrow, Howard, 1956, 117 (Box 18)
- Annual Federal Report, 1954-1955, 118 (Box 18)
- Annual Report - Research - Dept. of Cons., 1955-1956, 119 (Box 18)
- Monthly Reports - Winch, Hamilton, Clark, Swanson, 1952, 120 (Box 18)
- Monthly Reports - Winch, Hamilton, Clark, 1953, 121 (Box 18)
- Monthly Reports - Kellogg, Ayers, Swanson, Hewitt, L.S. Hamilton, W.J. Hamilton, 1954, 122 (Box 18)
- Monthly Reports - Winch, Hamilton, Clark, Cunningham, Brumsted, 1954, 123 (Box 18)
- Monthly Reports - Winch, Cunningham, Brumsted, Kellogg, Ayers, Morrow, 1955, 124 (Box 18)
- Circular Letter File - Wilson F. Clark, 1949-1954; Harlan Brumsted, 1954-1959, 125 (Box 18)
- New York State Conservation Training Camp Brochures, 126 (Box 18)
- Maple Products - Photographs, 127 (Box 18)
- Woodlots - Albany County through Orange Coounty, 1909-1928, 128 (Box 18)
- Robert Daniel Bell - Thesis - Maple Products in New York State, 1955, 129 (Box 18)
- Fulton County - Woodlot Management, 130 (Box 19)
- Forest Management Type Map - Keith Matteson - Otsego, 131 (Box 19)
- Merle Hall - Chautauqua County - Woodlot Management, 132 (Box 19)
- Oswego County Forestry Tour, 133 (Box 19)
- Great Bear Springs Farm - Oswego County, 134 (Box 19)
- Oneida County - Reforestation and 4-H, 135 (Box 19)
- Onondaga County - Forestry and 4-H, 136 (Box 19)
- Orange County - Forestry and 4-H, 137 (Box 19)
- Orleans County - Reforestation and Fence Posts, 138 (Box 19)
- Ostego County Forestry Tour, Dec. 9, 1948, 139 (Box 19)
- Otsego County - Extension, 140 (Box 19)
- Richford Springs - Van Hornesville Project, 141 (Box 19)
- Notes on Planting, 142 (Box 19)
- Poplar Planting, 143 (Box 19)
- Formation of Peat, 144 (Box 19)
- Forest Policy, 145 (Box 19)
- Plantings - Clippings, 146 (Box 19)
- Forest Fire - Protection, 147 (Box 19)
- Posts - White - Durability Record, 148 (Box 19)
- Pulpwood, 149 (Box 19)
- Pulp and Paper Companies in Pennsylvania, 150 (Box 19)
- Putnam Co. - Reforestation, 151 (Box 19)
- Pulp and Paper Manufacture - New York, 152 (Box 19)
- Rain Tree - Samanea Samen, 153 (Box 19)
- California Redwood, 154 (Box 19)
- Rensselaer County - Reforestation, 155 (Box 19)
- Rockland County - Logging, Reforestation, San Jose Scale, 156 (Box 19)
- Research on Natural Seeding, 157 (Box 19)
- Rural Economics and Sociology, 158 (Box 19)
- Rustic Fences, 159 (Box 19)
- Rustic Work - Manufacture, 160 (Box 19)
- Sawdust Utilization, 161 (Box 19)
- Sassafras Oil, 162 (Box 19)
- St. Lawrence County - Reforestation, 163 (Box 19)
- Saratoga County - Reforestation, 164 (Box 19)
- Schenectady County - Reforestation, 165 (Box 19)
- Saws, 166 (Box 19)
- Sawflies - Control, 167 (Box 19)
- Sawmill Machinery, 168 (Box 19)
- Scaling and Crushing Sticks, 169 (Box 19)
- Schoharie County - Reforestation, 170 (Box 19)
- School Forests, 171 (Box 19)
- Schuyler County - Reforestation, 172 (Box 19)
- Seashore Planting, 173 (Box 19)
- Seed Sources, 174 (Box 19)
- Scout Material (Boy Scouts), 175 (Box 19)
- Seed Collection Techniques, 176 (Box 19)
- Seneca County - Woodlot Management, 177 (Box 19)
- Schenectady County - Fagan's Highland Park, 178 (Box 19)
- City of Schenectady (watershed) - Schenectady County, 179 (Box 19)
- Shade and Street Trees, 180 (Box 19)
- Books on Shade and Street Trees, 181 (Box 19)
- Shade Trees - Injury from Dust, Smoke, etc., 182 (Box 19)
- Shipmast Locust, 183 (Box 19)
- Smokey the Bear - Publicity, 184 (Box 19)
- U.S. Forest Service - Small Woodland Owners Meeting, 185 (Box 19)
- Snow Damage to Conifer Plantations, 186 (Box 19)
- Soil Bank - USDA, 187 (Box 19)
- Soil Conservation Service - Planting of Shrubs, 188 (Box 19)
- Classification of Soils, 189 (Box 19)
- Steuben County - Woodlots, 190 (Box 19)
- Spruce Gall Aphids, 191 (Box 19)
- Suffolk County - Reforestation, 192 (Box 19)
- Sullivan County - Reforestation, 193 (Box 19)
- Forest in Sweden, 194 (Box 19)
- Tree Surgury - Repair materials, guards, trimming, 195 (Box 19)
- Summer School, 196 (Box 19)
- Woodland Report Forms - Soil Conservation Service, 197 (Box 19)
- Tannin, American - Sumac as a Source of Material, 198 (Box 19)
- Tanbark, 199 (Box 19)
- Taraktogenos Kurzii - Chaulmoogra Oil Source - Leprosy, 200 (Box 19)
- Fisher Tax Law, 201 (Box 19)
- Talks of Inspiration, Information, 202 (Box 19)
- Taxation of Farm Woodlands, 203 (Box 19)
- Forest Taxation, 204 (Box 19)
- The Principles of Forest Taxation, 205 (Box 19)
- Timber Distribution, 206 (Box 19)
- Tioga County - Woodlots, Agriculture, 207 (Box 19)
- Tompkins County - Forestry, Topo Map - Enfield Glen, 208 (Box 19)
- List of Trees Considered in Botany 2, 209 (Box 19)
- Tree Cavities, 210 (Box 19)
- Tree Surgeons, 211 (Box 19)
- Big Trees, 212 (Box 19)
- Unemployment, 213 (Box 19)
- Uses of Ironwood, 214 (Box 19)
- Umbrella Handle Stock, 215 (Box 19)
- Utlization - Forest Products, 216 (Box 19)
- Ulster Co. - Reforestation, 217 (Box 19)
- Lecture Notes on Wood Utilization, 218 (Box 19)
- Volume Tables, 219 (Box 19)
- Warren County - Forestry, 220 (Box 19)
- Washington County - Forestry, 221 (Box 19)
- Wayne County - Forestry, 222 (Box 19)
- Weather Data, 1959, 223 (Box 19)
- Westchester County - Forestry, 224 (Box 19)
- English Walnuts, 225 (Box 19)
- Black Walnuts, 226 (Box 19)
- White Pine Blister Rust - B.R. Agents State Report - Monthly, 227 (Box 19)
- White Pine Blister Rust, 228 (Box 19)
- Willow Culture, possible returns, 229 (Box 19)
- Wind Breaks and Hedges, 230 (Box 19)
- Wintergreen Oil from Birch Trees, 231 (Box 19)
- Winter Injury and Sun Scald, 232 (Box 19)
- Wich Hazel, 233 (Box 19)
- Woodchips, 244 (Box 19)
- Wood Gas, 245 (Box 19)
- Grain in Wood - Cross and Spiral Grain, 246 (Box 19)
- Wood Preservation, 247 (Box 19)
- Wood - Weight of Various Species, 248 (Box 20)
- Woodlot Statistics, 249 (Box 20)
- Wood Chopping Publicity, 250 (Box 20)
- Caring for the Growing Woodlot, 251 (Box 20)
- Forestry Articles, 1920-1921; 252 (Box 20)
- Woodlot Products, 1921-1934; 253 (Box 20)
- Wood Floor (Kressman), 254 (Box 20)
- Working Plan Cutting Tract, 255 (Box 20)
- Wyoming County - Land Use Program, 256 (Box 20)
- Yates County - Miscellaneous articles, 1928-1929; 257 (Box 20)
- Ten Year Plots Remeasured, Cope, 1938-1940; 258 (Box 20)
- Creosote - Koppers Company, 259 (Box 20)
- Cresote - Reilly Tar and Chemical Corp., 260 (Box 20)
- Osmose - Osmose Wood Preserving Company, 261 (Box 20)
- Maple Articles, 262 (Box 20)
- Western New York Forestry Tour, 1957; 263 (Box 20)
- Adirondack Tour, 1951; 264 (Box 20)
- Adirondack Tour, 1952, 265 (Box 20)
- Adirondack Tour, 1950, 266 (Box 20)
- Adirondack Tour, 1949, 267 (Box 20)
- Adirondack Tour, 1948, 268 (Box 20)
- Adirondack Tour, 1942, 269 (Box 20)
- Adirondack Tour, 1941, 270 (Box 20)
- Adirondack Tour, 1940, 271 (Box 20)
- Adirondack Tour, 1939, 272 (Box 20)
- Albany County Forestry Program, 1918-1954, 273 (Box 20)
- Allegany County Forestry Program, 1920-1956, 274 (Box 20)
- Broome County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 275 (Box 20)
- Cattaraugus County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 276 (Box 20)
- Cayuga County Forestry Program, 1918-1956, 277 (Box 20)
- Chatauqua County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 278 (Box 20)
- Chenango County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 279 (Box 20)
- Chemung County Forestry Program, 1920-1956, 280 (Box 20)
- Clinton County Forestry Program, 1926-1956, 281 (Box 20)
- Columbia County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 282 (Box 20)
- Cortland County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 283 (Box 20)
- Delaware County Forestry Program, 1921-1956, 284 (Box 20)
- Dutchess County Forestry Program, 1919-1954, 285 (Box 20)
- Erie County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 286 (Box 20)
- Essex County Forestry Program, 1918-1956, 287 (Box 20)
- Franklin County Forestry Program, 1928-1956, 288 (Box 20)
- Fulton County Forestry Program, 1922-1956, 289 (Box 20)
- Genesee County Forestry Program, 1922-1956, 290 (Box 20)
- Greene County Forestry Program, 1925-1956, 291 (Box 20)
- Hamilton County Forestry Program, 1950-1956, 292 (Box 20)
- Herkimer County Forestry Program, 1919-1955, 293 (Box 20)
- Jefferson County Forestry Program, 1947-1956, 294 (Box 20)
- Lewis County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 295 (Box 20)
- Livingston County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 296 (Box 20)
- Madison County Forestry Program, 1920-1955, 297 (Box 20)
- Monroe County Forestry Program, 1918-1956, 298 (Box 20)
- Montgomery County Forestry Program, 1925-1956, 299 (Box 20)
- Nassau County Forestry Program, 1919-1953, 300 (Box 20)
- New York City Forestry Program, 1918-1950, 301 (Box 20)
- Niagara County Forestry Program, 1922-1956, 302 (Box 20)
- Oneida County Forestry Program, 1919-1955, 303 (Box 20)
- Onondaga County Forestry Program, 1918-1956, 304 (Box 20)
- Ontario County Forestry Program, 1921-1956, 305 (Box 20)
- Orange County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 306 (Box 20)
- Orleans County Forestry Program, 1927-1953, 307 (Box 20)
- Oswego County Forestry Program, 1926-1956, 308 (Box 20)
- Otsego County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 309 (Box 20)
- Philadelphia, PA visits, 1950-1952, 310 (Box 20)
- Putman County Forestry Program, 1923-1941, 311 (Box 20)
- Rockland County Forestry Program, 1925-1954, 312 (Box 20)
- Rensselaer County Forestry Program, 1921-1955, 313 (Box 20)
- Saratoga County Forestry Program, 1926-1956, 314 (Box 20)
- Schenectady County Forestry Program, 1925-1956, 315 (Box 20)
- Schoharie County Forestry Program, 1922-1955, 316 (Box 20)
- Schuyler County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 317 (Box 20)
- St. Lawrence County Forestry Program, 1921-1956, 318 (Box 20)
- Seneca County Forestry Program, 1918-1953, 319 (Box 20)
- Steuben County Forestry Program, 1925-1956, 320 (Box 20)
- Suffolk County Forestry Program, 1922-1951, 321 (Box 20)
- Sullivan County Forestry Program, 1924-1953, 322 (Box 20)
- Tioga County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 323 (Box 20)
- Tompkins County Forestry Program, 1918-1956, 324 (Box 20)
- Ulster County Forestry Program, 1919-1951, 325 (Box 20)
- Warren County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 326 (Box 20)
- Washington D.C. Visits, 1942-1950, 327 (Box 20)
- Washington County Forestry Program, 1920-1956, 328 (Box 20)
- Wayne County Forestry Program, 1924-1956, 329 (Box 20)
- Westchester County Forestry Program, 1920-1950, 330 (Box 20)
- Wyoming County Forestry Program, 1919-1956, 331 (Box 20)
- Yates County Forestry Program, 1924-1955, 332 (Box 20)
- Economic Evaluation, Maple Syrup Production, 1969, 333 (Box 20)
- Maple Syrup Production in the New York State, 1970, 334 (Box 20)
- Journal of Forestry, 335 (Box 20)
- Maple Syrup, 1962-1964, 336 (Box 20)
- Forestry Teaching Outlines, 337 (Box 20)
- Chestnut Planting - Japanese and Chinese, 338 (Box 20)
- Plantations and Windbreak, Varna, 339 (Box 20)
- Hardwood Planting, Salisbury Farm, 340 (Box 20)
- Balsam Briefs, 1972-1973, 341 (Box 20)
- Article 20-C, Agriculture and Markets Law, 342 (Box 20)
- Soil Maps, 343 (Box 20)
- Enviornmental Education Booklets, 344 (Box 20)
- Resource Inventory, Plymoth County, Mass., 345 (Box 20)
- Christmas Tree Growers' Convention Program; 1970, 1972, 346 (Box 20)
- Private Campgrounds as Alternative Land Use, 347 (Box 20)
- Woodlot Management Ideas, 348 (Box 21)
- Research Notes, Northeastern Experimental Station, 349 (Box 21)
- Research Notes, Adirondack Allegheny Experimental Station, 350 (Box 21)
- Pennsylvania State College Experiment Station, 1949, 351 (Box 21)
- Adirondack Park Land Use Map, 352 (Box 21)
- Notes on Forest Investigations, Albany, 1937-1942, 353 (Box 21)
- Leaf Disposal Project, 1968, 354 (Box 21)
- List of Markets and Wood-using Industries, Boonville, 355 (Box 21)
- U.S.F.S. Region 7, Statement of Objectives, 1938, 356 (Box 21)
- 1940 Agricultural Conservation Program in New York, 357 (Box 21)
- Forest Products Laboratory Publications, 1942-1944, 358 (Box 21)
- Forestry Research, Montana and California, 359 (Box 21)
- Beech Utilization Series, 1951, 360 (Box 21)
- University of Illinois, Agricultural Experiment Station, 1951-1960, 361 (Box 21)
- Fox Forest Notes, New Hampshire, 1946-1956, 362 (Box 21)
- Indiana, Vermont Cooperative Extension Forestry Notes, 1952-1953, 363 (Box 21)
- University of Maine, Techincal Notes, 1950-1958, 364 (Box 21)
- Lake States Forest Experiment Station, 1946-1951, 365 (Box 21)
- Lake States Forest Experiment Station Technical Notes, 366 (Box 21)
- Northeastern Forest Experiment Station Papers, 1946-1953, 367 (Box 21)
- Notes on Forest Investigations, New York, 1942, 368 (Box 21)
- Materials Survey, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, 1950, 369 (Box 21)
- New York State Forest Marketing Bulletin, 1946, 370 (Box 21)
- U.S.D.A. Report on Research, Service and Marketing Education, 1950, 371 (Box 21)
- U.S.F.S. Region 7, Statement of Objectives, 1937, 372 (Box 22)
- Plan of Action, Tioga-Chemung Project, 1942, 373 (Box 22)
- Plan of Action, Hudson Valley Project, 1942, 374 (Box 22)
- Log Grades and Lumber Grades (Bankhead-Jones Act), 1937, 375 (Box 22)
- Forest Products Laboratory Publications, 1940-1942, 376 (Box 22)
- Administrative Procedures, Cooperative Forest Management Act of 1950, 377 (Box 22)
- New York State Joint Legislative Committee on Interstate Cooperation, 1950, 378 (Box 22)
- New York State County Plantations, 1909-1925, 379 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: 1950's, 380 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: 1954-1960, incl. Recknagel Memorial, 381 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Sanitary Building, June 1957-July 1957, 382 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Main Lodge, Fall 1962-Spring 1962, 383 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 1, Niagra County Federation of Sport Clubs, Oct. 1954, 384 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 2, Townanda Sport Club, Oct. 1954, 385 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 3, May 1955, 386 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 4, Sports Federation, May 1955, 387 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 5, Waverly Sports Club, May 1955-June 1955, 388 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 6, Erie Co. Sport ALliance, June 1955, 389 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 7, Quaphegvo, Aug. 1955, 390 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 8, So. New York Fish and Game Association, Westchester Cornell University Conservation Club, Oct. 1955-Nov. 1955, 391 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 9, Kiwanis - Elmira Heights, June 1956, 392 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 10, Kiwains - Ithaca, May 1957, 393 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 11, Tioga Woodland Owners Coop., May 1957, 394 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabin 12, Genesee Conservation League, Monroe County, June 1960, 395 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Research, 396 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: 4-H Camp, Teacher's Workshop, 397 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Cabins, 398 (Box 22)
- Landowner Signs, 399 (Box 22)
- Arnot Forest Photos: Mounted Enlargements, 400 (Box 22)
- Misc. Photos: Wetlands, Tree Farms, 401 (Box 23)
- Conservation Course I Photos, 402 (Box 23)
- Conservation Course I Photos, 403 (Box 23)
- Pesticides Photos, 404 (Box 23)
- Photos: New Yokr State Barge Canal, 405 (Box 23)
- Water Pollution Photos, 406 (Box 23)
- Land in a New Light Photos, 407 (Box 23)
- Photos for Forest Preserve MS, 408 (Box 23)
- B and W Photos Mounted 1960, F and H WK. - Fishing, 409 (Box 23)
- Assorted Mounted Photos, 410 (Box 23)
- NY DEC Photos, 411 (Box 23)
- Bird Photos: Inviting Bird Neighbors, Humphrey Press, 412 (Box 23)
- NY DEC Photos: Mounted, 413 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1947, 414 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1950, 415 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1952, 416 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1953, 417 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1954, 418 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1955, 419 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1956 (1-30), 420 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1956 (1-56 and negatives), 421 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1957 (1-30), 422 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1957 (31-60), 423 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1957 (61-90), 424 (Box 23)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1957 (91-94 and negatives), 425 (Box 24)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1958 (1-30), 426 (Box 24)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1958 (31-57 and negatives), 427 (Box 24)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1959, 428 (Box 24)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1959 (extra photos), 429 (Box 24)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1960 (1-30), 430 (Box 24)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1960 (31-60), 431 (Box 24)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos, 1960 (61-75 and negatives), 432 (Box 24)
- Arnot 4-H Camp Photos; 1961, 1965 (boys, 1965, girls, photos), 433 (Box 24)
- Long Island Marine District Workshop, 1959, 434 (Box 24)
- Sportsman Workshop Photos, 1955, (1-33), 435 (Box 24)
- Sportsman Workshop Photos, 1955 (34-78 and negatives), 436 (Box 24)
- Sportsman Workshop, Allegany State Park, 1956 (photos 1-30), 437 (Box 24)
- Sportsman Workshop, Allegany State Park, 1956 (photos 31-60), 438 (Box 25)
- Sportsman Workshop, Allegany State Park, 1956 (photos 61-67 and negatives), 439 (Box 25)
- Sportsman Workshop, Croton-on-Hudson, 1957 (photos 1-30), 440 (Box 25)
- Sportsman Workshop, Croton-on-Hudson, 1957 (photos 31-46 and negatives), 441 (Box 25)
- Sportsman Workshop, Geneva, 1957 (photos), 442 (Box 25)
- Sportsman Workshop, Bristol Hills, 1958 (photos), 443 (Box 25)
- Sportsman Workshop, Kemptville Ontario, 1959 (photos 1-30), 444 (Box 25)
- Sportsman Workshop, Kemptville Ontario, 1959 (photos 31-48 and negatives), 445 (Box 25)
- Adirondack Tour, 1955-1961 (photos), 446 (Box 25)
- Sportsman Workshop, 1960 (photos), 447 (Box 25)
- Sportsman Workshop, 1961 (photos), 448 (Box 25)
- Conservation Leaders Workshop, Sportsman Workshop, 1963 (photos), 449 (Box 25)
- Sportsman Workshop, 1964 (photos), 450 (Box 25)
- Summary of Farm and Home Week, 1952, 451 (Box 25)
- Summary of Farm and Home Week, 1953, 452 (Box 25)
- Progress Report - Cooperative Research Between Soil Conservation Service and New York Agricultural Experiment Station - Color Slides of Arnot Wood Lots, 1939 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Cambodia's Off-Shore Marine Fishery- Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Conservation Field Day Programs, 1975-1996 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Conservation Field Day Programs, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Conservation Newsletter, 1968-1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Cooperative Extension- Correspondence, Meetings re: Program Planning, 1986-1990 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Department of Conservation Extension Meeting, 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Dep't of Natural Resources, 1916- 1953 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Fisheries in the Lower Mekong Basin Annexes (Color Photos), May 1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Fisheries Management in the Tonle Sap Lake Ecosystem of Cambodia, (n.d.) (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Initiative for Future Agriculture and Food Systems, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Life Cycles, Standing Stocks and Drifts, (n.d.) (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Natural Resources Allocation Proceedings, December 14, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Minn. Meeting- N.R. Extension Conference, May 1998 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Natural Resources Symposium, 1981-1995 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Natural Resources and Enviornmental Management (NREM) Awards, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- NREM Award- Correspondence, 1995- 1997 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- NREM Base Program Strategic Terms- Correspondence, Notes, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- NREM Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- NREM- Budgets, Grants, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- NREM- Buffalo Meeting, September 1998 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- NREM Conference Call- Minutes, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- NRES NREM Conference Call, 1998-2001 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- NREM- Correspondence, Budget, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- NREM- Correspondence, Reports, Meeting Programs, 1999-2001 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- NREM- Correspondence, Grants, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- NREM- Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- NREM- Correspondence, 1997-1999 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- NREM- Correspondence, Notes, Contact Lists, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- NREM- Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- NREM- General Correspondence, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Misc. Correspondence, Reports, 1967-1997 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- NREM Flagship 1999, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- NREM Flagship Process, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- NREM Flagship- Directory, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- NREM- General Items, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- NREM Grants- Correspondence, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- NREM Mailing Lists for South, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- NE NREM Meeting, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- NREM Meeting- Denver, Colo., December 5-7, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- NREM Fall Meeting, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- NREM- Minnesota Expenses, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- NREM- NASULGC Annual Meeting (Atlanta), 1998 (Box 27, Folder 42)
- NREM National Meeting, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- NREM Flagship Program- Correspondence, Grants, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- NREM Newsletter, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- NREM- Possible News, 1996-2000 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- NREM- Program Leadership Conference, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- NREM- Screening, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 48)